{
    "subject": "resource/Oliver_Twist_(2005_film)",
    "predicate": "ontology/starring",
    "object": "resource/Ben_Kingsley",
    "human_readable": "Ben Kingsley stars in the film Oliver Twist (2005).",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9340395331382751,
            "question": "Who starred in the film Oliver Twist (2005)?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8208336234092712,
            "question": "Who directed the film Oliver Twist (2005)?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7364734411239624,
            "question": "In what film did Ben Kingsley appear?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7193756103515625,
            "question": "What other famous films has Ben Kingsley starred in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6610121726989746,
            "question": "What is the genre of the film Oliver Twist (2005)?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5708925127983093,
            "question": "Is Ben Kingsley known for his roles in dramas or comedies?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5558024048805237,
            "question": "Name another actor who has played the character of Oliver Twist."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5093653202056885,
            "question": "What year was the film Oliver Twist released?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2599983215332031,
            "question": "Has Ben Kingsley won any awards for his acting?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.16458627581596375,
            "question": "What is a common theme explored in Charles Dickens's novel Oliver Twist?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Ben Kingsley stars in the film Oliver Twist (2005).",
            "html": "dbpedia_8184_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Has Ben Kingsley won any awards for his acting?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8184_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What year was the film Oliver Twist released?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8184_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Name another actor who has played the character of Oliver Twist.",
            "html": "dbpedia_8184_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8184_16.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8184_19.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8184_21.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8184_28.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8184_29.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8184_31.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8184_35.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8184_40.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8184_44.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8184_7.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'} \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provided contain information that supports Ben Kingsley starring in the film \u201cOliver Twist\u201d (2005). Specifically, document 7.txt mentions, \u201cSir Ben Kingsley will portray Fagin and 10-year-old British actor Barney Clark will star as Oliver.\u201d This confirms his role in the film."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Extremely Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}